

瑪彼德

MORGANTI PIETRO

ITC



Phone

+886 966770245



Address

Kaohsiung City, 842 - Taiwan



Email

pietro.morganti@gmail.com



LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/pietro-morganti

About me

I'm from Italy and currently live in Taiwan, Oi Shan,

Since I was a teenager my family and I have been in a close relationship with the oriental world, we lived in Shanghai for several years.

This chapter of my life influenced also my own character: I am polite, social, outgoing, hardworking, and also a very sportive person.

Professional Skills

Web Development

Intermediate

Graphic Designer

Intermediate

SEO

Basic

Adobe Pack.

Intermediate

Microsoft Office Pack.

Intermediate

Professional Skills

Italian

Native

English

Advanced

Chinese

Basic

Spanish

Basic

Interests

- Soccer
- **Watching Movies**
- Swimming

Education Background

2019 - 2022 University of Shih Chien

IEET - Technology Information

2014 - 2018

Istituto Commerciale "Corinaldesi"

Diploma - Programmer accountant

Work Experiences

2019-2020

Intern - Shih Chien University Libraty

Kaohsiung, Taiwan, TW

09/2017

Intern - Akash Indian Restaurant

• Portsmouth, England, UK

06/2017

Intern as a programmer - Loccioni

Angeli di Rosora (AN), Italy, IT

03/2017

Intern as a programmer - Logical System

Jesi (AN), Italy, IT

08/2016

Staff team - YOUTH GAMES 2016

Ancona (AN), Italy, IT

08/2015

Intern - Parkwest Flowers

Mallow, Ireland, IE

WORK EXPERIENCES

2019-2020

Intern - Shih Chien University Libraty

Kaohsiung, Taiwan, TW - https://lib.usc.edu.tw/

 My job is to stay at the reception and arrange the books when required. I have the opportunity to improve my Chinese and above all the opportunity to improve my skills in talking to customers.

09/2017

Intern - Akash Indian Restaurant

Portsmouth, England, UK - https://www.theakash.co.uk/

 I had this opportunity thanks to an Erasmus job grant. I worked at The Akash as an intern, office jobs and advertising. It helped me a lot in developing my English language skills.

06/2017

Intern as a programmer - Loccioni

Angeli di Rosora (AN), Italy, IT - https://www.theakash.co.uk/

Is a work experience for school students. I followed the OCR project (creation or modification from Layouts) and studied JavaScript program language. It was my first time in the world of work. It helped me understand what it is to work, respect schedules and deadlines but also how to get a result.

03/2017

Intern as a programmer - Logical System

Jesi (AN), Italy, IT - https://www.logicalsystem.it/en/

• Is a work experience for school students. I Elaborated and implemented a project with everything related to it.

08/2016

Staff team - YOUTH GAMES 2016

Ancona (AN), Italy, IT - https://www.facebook.com/animusyouthgames

• It was a sporting event in which we welcomed and helped all the foreign sports teams participating in the competitions.

08/2015

Intern - Parkwest Flowers

Mallow, Ireland, IE - https://www.mallowflowers.com/

• I had this opportunity thanks to an Erasmus job grant. Help students understand what it meant to work in Europe.